<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on foursight</title>
    <link>https://incub4t0r.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on foursight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:05:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://incub4t0r.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>malga</title>
      <link>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/malga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 17:05:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/malga/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR Had an old Fire Tablet laying around, repurposed it as a web weather app display.
But why? Everyday, too much technology is thrown out to be collected in landfills around the world. Even if it&amp;rsquo;s just me, I wanted to take part in reducing the landfill, device by device.
Development Key points
 Has to be responsive to multiple device screens Has to show time, date, and weather  APIs used</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Your Base Are Belong To Us</title>
      <link>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/allyourbasebelongtous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 17:05:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/allyourbasebelongtous/</guid>
      <description>This problem cost me 5 years of my life. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been this hard, but here we go.
TL;DR When you netcat to the provided web address, you are given this output.
 This program is going to ask you to convert among 6 different bases a total of 5 times. Each question is placed inside of lines delimited by 78&#39;-&#39; characters. The first line of each question indicates the base we aregiving to you as well as the base we expect the result in and looks like:[src_base] -&amp;gt; [answer base]The next line of the question is the source text that we want you to convertinto the new base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>angstromCTF - Image Encryption</title>
      <link>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/angstromimageencryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 17:05:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://incub4t0r.github.io/posts/angstromimageencryption/</guid>
      <description>This was a fun one, it required me to annotate the source code and figure out a decryption method for the given picture.
TL;DR The file image-encryption.py is opening a target image file, in this case, img.png.
The program then creates an array of the pixels that the image contains, then parses through each pixel. Upon arriving at each pixel, the program then stores into a variable what is assumably the RGB values of each pixel.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
